
export const quizQuestions_8 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is create-react-app?',
    choices: ['A JavaScript library for building user interfaces', 'A toolchain for building React applications', 'A component library for React', 'An online React code editor'],
    correctAnswer: 'A toolchain for building React applications',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you create a new React application using create-react-app?',
    choices: ['npm create react-app my-app', 'create-react-app new my-app', 'react-create-app my-app', 'npm init react-app my-app'],
    correctAnswer: 'npm create react-app my-app',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the purpose of the "public" folder in a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['To store static assets like images and fonts', 'To define global styles for the entire application', 'To host the main HTML file', 'To keep private configuration files'],
    correctAnswer: 'To store static assets like images and fonts',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you start the development server in a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['npm build', 'npm start', 'npm serve', 'npm dev'],
    correctAnswer: 'npm start',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which command is used to build a production-ready version of a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['npm compile', 'npm build', 'npm prod', 'npm release'],
    correctAnswer: 'npm build',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the purpose of the "src" folder in a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['To store configuration files', 'To keep track of project dependencies', 'To define project scripts', 'To contain the source code of the React application'],
    correctAnswer: 'To contain the source code of the React application',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you install additional dependencies in a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['npm install', 'npm add', 'npm dependency', 'npm install --save'],
    correctAnswer: 'npm install',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the purpose of the ".env" files in a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['To configure environment variables', 'To store secret API keys', 'To define project scripts', 'To manage project dependencies'],
    correctAnswer: 'To configure environment variables',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which command is used to run tests in a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['npm test', 'npm run test', 'npm start-test', 'npm testing'],
    correctAnswer: 'npm test',
  },
  {
    question: 'How do you eject from a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['npm eject', 'npm exit', 'npm abandon', 'npm release'],
    correctAnswer: 'npm eject',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the purpose of the "build" folder in a create-react-app project?',
    choices: ['To store development files', 'To host the main HTML file', 'To store the compiled and minified production build', 'To keep track of project dependencies'],
    correctAnswer: 'To store the compiled and minified production build',
    },
  ],
}